<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifehacks on Maksim Tsiarokhin</title>
    <link>https://tsiarokhin.com/categories/lifehacks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifehacks on Maksim Tsiarokhin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 21:06:22 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tsiarokhin.com/categories/lifehacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to change D365FO environment tenant</title>
      <link>https://tsiarokhin.com/posts/change-d365fo-environment-tenant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 21:06:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tsiarokhin.com/posts/change-d365fo-environment-tenant/</guid>
      <description>Before application version 10.0.23, every dev box came with a tool called AdminUserProvisioning which could be found at K:\AOSService\PackagesLocalDirectory\bin\AdminUserProvisioning.exe. It was very useful to quickly make your account an Admin, especially after a database restore. The tool has since been removed and the recommended way now is to create a separate user for yourself and assign the System administrator role to it.
Add new userLink to headingBut how can you add a new user if you can&amp;rsquo;t access the environment?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You don&#39;t really need SysOperation controller</title>
      <link>https://tsiarokhin.com/posts/you-dont-need-sysoperation-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:54:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tsiarokhin.com/posts/you-dont-need-sysoperation-controller/</guid>
      <description>We all know the SysOperation framework - the successor to the RunBaseBatch. Whenever you need to add a new periodic job to the system you have to create the following items:
Service class, which contains the code to perform the processing; (Optional) Data contract class, which contains the parameters for the job; (Optional) UI builder class, which allows you to customize the look of the prompt dialog; Controller class, which configures how to run the job; Action menu item pointing to your controller to let users run the job and configure security.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
